Boston Streets Collection MS102
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Boston City Directories, 1845 -- 1925; 1845 -- 1960; MS102.002; 2703 Digital Object(s)
  - 1870, MS102.002.006; 527 Digital Object(s)
    - George W. Buss, Blacksmith & Wheelwright; C.R. Mclean, Millwright; Union Glass Company, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00194; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of George W. Buss, Blacksmith & Wheelwright; C.R. Mclean, Millwright; Union Glass Company from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Chickering & Sons, Pianos; I.P. Frink's Reflectors; J.H. Upham & Co., Goods, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00195; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Chickering & Sons, Pianos; I.P. Frink's Reflectors; J.H. Upham & Co., Goods from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00196; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00197; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Boston Sterotype Foundry, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00198; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Boston Sterotype Foundry from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - National Life Insurance Company of New York; A.T. Stearns & Sons, Lumber; Kimball Brothers, Carriages and Sleighs, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00199; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of National Life Insurance Company of New York; A.T. Stearns & Sons, Lumber; Kimball Brothers, Carriages and Sleighs from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Insurance Companies, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00200; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Insurance Companies from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Tremont Ear and Eye Institute; J.E. Poor & Co., Piano Movers; N.E. Linen Hose Manufacturing Company, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00201; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Tremont Ear and Eye Institute; J.E. Poor & Co., Piano Movers; N.E. Linen Hose Manufacturing Company from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00202; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Florence Sewing Machines; Novelty Manufacturing Company; J.W. Stickney & Co., Chalk; Wiliiam Carl, Painter and Decorator, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00203; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Florence Sewing Machines; Novelty Manufacturing Company; J.W. Stickney & Co., Chalk; Wiliiam Carl, Painter and Decorator from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00204; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Dorchester Mutual Fire Insurance Comapny; John Buckpitt, Harness Maker;; Hucthinson Bros., Furniture Manufactory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00205; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Dorchester Mutual Fire Insurance Comapny; John Buckpitt, Harness Maker;; Hucthinson Bros., Furniture Manufactory from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Cook, Rymes, & Co., Machinists, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00206; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Cook, Rymes, & Co., Machinists from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00207; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Carl Dittmar, Explosives; H.F. PArk, Provisions; S. Gleason, Undertaker; William H.Floyd, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00208; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Carl Dittmar, Explosives; H.F. PArk, Provisions; S. Gleason, Undertaker; William H.Floyd from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00209; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00210; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Owen Paper Company; Carlos Lanza, Merchant, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00211; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Owen Paper Company; Carlos Lanza, Merchant from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Buerk's Watchman Time Detector, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00212; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Buerk's Watchman Time Detector from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Buerk's Watchman Time Detector, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00213; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Engley & Rice, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00214; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Engley & Rice from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Bayside Liquid Soap; Pollard & Leighton, Military Goods; Hope & Whitney, Signs; McLaughlin Brush Manufactory, Murphy, Leavens, & Co., 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00215; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Bayside Liquid Soap; Pollard & Leighton, Military Goods; Hope & Whitney, Signs; McLaughlin Brush Manufactory, Murphy, Leavens, & Co. from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Blake's Steam Pump Factory, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00216; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Blake's Steam Pump Factory from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Mutual Life Insurance; Clark's Linen Hose; C. Keaser, Plumber; Clark & Leatherbee, Lumber, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00217; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Mutual Life Insurance; Clark's Linen Hose; C. Keaser, Plumber; Clark & Leatherbee, Lumber from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - American Tablet Co.; Hayden & Balcom, Leather Board; G.H. Loomis, Photographic Gallery, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00218; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of American Tablet Co.; Hayden & Balcom, Leather Board; G.H. Loomis, Photographic Gallery from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00219; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00220; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Huntoon Governor, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00221; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Huntoon Governor from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00222; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00223; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Alfred Hale & Co., India Rubber Goods, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00224; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Alfred Hale & Co., India Rubber Goods from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Buckley & Bancroft, Furniture, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00225; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Buckley & Bancroft, Furniture from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Institution for the Blind, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00226; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Institution for the Blind from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Sidney Fisher & Co.; Charles A. Brackett; Stephen Smith & Co.; Mrs. A.C. Latham, Physician & Dermatologist, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00227; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Sidney Fisher & Co.; Charles A. Brackett; Stephen Smith & Co.; Mrs. A.C. Latham, Physician & Dermatologist from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - James Collins & Co., Wines And Liquors; Sewing Machine Exchange; John Robbins, Baggage Checks; Dwight C. Robbins, Key Checks, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00228; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of James Collins & Co., Wines And Liquors; Sewing Machine Exchange; John Robbins, Baggage Checks; Dwight C. Robbins, Key Checks from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Roxbury Point Planing Mill; Taylor & Hutchinson; Tripp, Eddy, & Co., Boot and Shoe Machinery, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00229; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Roxbury Point Planing Mill; Taylor & Hutchinson; Tripp, Eddy, & Co., Boot and Shoe Machinery from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - J.R. Broadstreet, Rubber Moulding and Weatherstrips, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00230; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of J.R. Broadstreet, Rubber Moulding and Weatherstrips from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Dennisons & Co., Tags, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00231; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Dennisons & Co., Tags from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Isaac Colburn & Co., Boot and Shoe Machinery; Fairbanks & Bird Co., 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00232; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Isaac Colburn & Co., Boot and Shoe Machinery; Fairbanks & Bird Co. from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Parker & Gannett, Agricultural Warehouse; Henry W. Wilson, Civil Engineer & Surveyor; Foye & Gleason, Watches; Thos. H. McDonald, Plumber, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00233; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Parker & Gannett, Agricultural Warehouse; Henry W. Wilson, Civil Engineer & Surveyor; Foye & Gleason, Watches; Thos. H. McDonald, Plumber from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - J. Harris & Co., Weather-Vanes; William Butterfield, Sewing Machines; Joseph Carew's Marble & Stone Works, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00234; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of J. Harris & Co., Weather-Vanes; William Butterfield, Sewing Machines; Joseph Carew's Marble & Stone Works from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Foundry And Machine Company, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00235; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Foundry And Machine Company from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Taunton & Boston Express; Samuel Colby's Clothing Store, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00236; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Taunton & Boston Express; Samuel Colby's Clothing Store from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Taunton Iron Works Co.; J.R. Williams, Fire Brick; H. Allen, Moving; L. Brynes, Fancy Turnings, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00237; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Taunton Iron Works Co.; J.R. Williams, Fire Brick; H. Allen, Moving; L. Brynes, Fancy Turnings from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Crompton & Dawson; Albert F. Allen, Fire Department Supplies; Butler, Brown, & Co.; Curtiss & Arnold, gold & Silver Refiners, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00238; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Crompton & Dawson; Albert F. Allen, Fire Department Supplies; Butler, Brown, & Co.; Curtiss & Arnold, gold & Silver Refiners from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Sumner Pratt & Co., General Supply; Sargent Card Clothing Co.; A. Field & Sons, Copper and Iron Tacks, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00239; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Sumner Pratt & Co., General Supply; Sargent Card Clothing Co.; A. Field & Sons, Copper and Iron Tacks from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Washburn & Moen Mfg. Co., 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00240; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Washburn & Moen Mfg. Co. from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Lucius W. Pond, Machinists' Tools, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00241; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Lucius W. Pond, Machinists' Tools from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Crompton Loom Works, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00242; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Crompton Loom Works from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Holmes & Blanchard, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00243; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Holmes & Blanchard from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00244; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - G.H. Gorley, Cement; Dr. J. Wesley Kelley; Rogers, Smith, & Co., Roofers, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00245; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of G.H. Gorley, Cement; Dr. J. Wesley Kelley; Rogers, Smith, & Co., Roofers from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00246; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - S.K. Taylor & Co., Cutting Dies; J. & J. Kohler & Co., Patretn Double Chamber Hot-Air Furnace, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00247; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of S.K. Taylor & Co., Cutting Dies; J. & J. Kohler & Co., Patretn Double Chamber Hot-Air Furnace from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - A.O. Corbett, Railroad, Steamship, and Machinists' Supplies, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00248; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of A.O. Corbett, Railroad, Steamship, and Machinists' Supplies from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00249; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Belt & Leather Stuffing Co.; J.W. Stackpole, Dealer in Oils; V.J. Messigner & Co., Silk Manufacturers; H.S. Shepard & Chester, Lumber, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00250; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Belt & Leather Stuffing Co.; J.W. Stackpole, Dealer in Oils; V.J. Messigner & Co., Silk Manufacturers; H.S. Shepard & Chester, Lumber from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Charles H. Bruce, Window Shades; Hill & Wright, Coopers; Eben B. Phillips & Co., Oils, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00251; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Charles H. Bruce, Window Shades; Hill & Wright, Coopers; Eben B. Phillips & Co., Oils from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - American Button-Hole & Overseaming Sewing Machine; A. Wilbur & Co., Roofing Supplies; Wyman & Arklay, Linens, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00252; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of American Button-Hole & Overseaming Sewing Machine; A. Wilbur & Co., Roofing Supplies; Wyman & Arklay, Linens from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - James Martin & Son, Tnets; Hinckley & Co., Roofing Materials; Dewson, Williams, & Co., Merchants, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00253; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of James Martin & Son, Tnets; Hinckley & Co., Roofing Materials; Dewson, Williams, & Co., Merchants from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00254; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00255; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - American Tool and Machine Co., 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00256; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of American Tool and Machine Co. from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - S.A. Woods & Co.s' Machinery Depot; Newcomb & Brown, Apothecaries; Delaporte & Blumberg, Chairs; International Hotel, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00257; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of S.A. Woods & Co.s' Machinery Depot; Newcomb & Brown, Apothecaries; Delaporte & Blumberg, Chairs; International Hotel from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Harrison Loring, Iron Ship Building, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00258; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Harrison Loring, Iron Ship Building from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Isaac F. Dobson, Marine & Fire Insurance, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00259; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Isaac F. Dobson, Marine & Fire Insurance from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Fire & Marine Insurance, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00260; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Fire & Marine Insurance from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Marine and Inland Navigation Risks, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00261; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Marine and Inland Navigation Risks from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00262; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - George Coolridge, Invention Agent and Publisher, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00263; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of George Coolridge, Invention Agent and Publisher from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Torrent Rotary Pumps, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00264; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Torrent Rotary Pumps from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Novelty Wood Works, J.J. McNutt; American House, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00265; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Novelty Wood Works, J.J. McNutt; American House from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00266; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00267; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00268; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00269; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Waverley House, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00270; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Waverley House from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00271; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00272; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Edwin A. Rogers, Varnishes; The Isham bank Lock; Abbott's Liquid Soap, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00273; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Edwin A. Rogers, Varnishes; The Isham bank Lock; Abbott's Liquid Soap from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Rusell Hallett, Piano-Fortes; Welch, Harrison, & Co. Pattern and Model Makers; Thos. Johnson, Grocer, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00274; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Rusell Hallett, Piano-Fortes; Welch, Harrison, & Co. Pattern and Model Makers; Thos. Johnson, Grocer from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00275; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - H.N.F. Marshall & Co., Lubricating Oils; Hall Manufacturing Co.; Glibert Wait, Real Estate Agent; Henry Moulton & Co., Ladders, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00276; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of H.N.F. Marshall & Co., Lubricating Oils; Hall Manufacturing Co.; Glibert Wait, Real Estate Agent; Henry Moulton & Co., Ladders from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Howard Foundry and Machine Works; H.A. Perry, Painter; M.M. Knapp, Optician; Anders' Magneto-Telegraph Construction Co., 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00277; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Howard Foundry and Machine Works; H.A. Perry, Painter; M.M. Knapp, Optician; Anders' Magneto-Telegraph Construction Co. from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Knowles' Patent Steam Pump, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00278; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Knowles' Patent Steam Pump from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00279; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - New York Steam Engine Company, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00280; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of New York Steam Engine Company from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - E.T. Cowdrey & Co.; Drs. Pratt & Woodman; E.W. Griggs, Baker; Smith, Merrill, & Co., Oils, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00281; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of E.T. Cowdrey & Co.; Drs. Pratt & Woodman; E.W. Griggs, Baker; Smith, Merrill, & Co., Oils from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00282; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00283; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00284; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00285; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00286; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Empire Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York; Pickens & Washburn, Planing & Moulding Mill; Eaton & Ayer, Boobins, Spools, & Shuttles, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00287; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Empire Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York; Pickens & Washburn, Planing & Moulding Mill; Eaton & Ayer, Boobins, Spools, & Shuttles from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00288; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00289; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00290; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00291; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Eagle Printing Ink Works, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00292; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Eagle Printing Ink Works from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00293; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00294; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00295; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Chase's Spring Bed, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00296; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Chase's Spring Bed from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00297; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - J.N. Lindsay & Co., Silver Plating; John Souther & Co., Steam Excavators and Dredges, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00298; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of J.N. Lindsay & Co., Silver Plating; John Souther & Co., Steam Excavators and Dredges from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - The New England Litogrphic Company; Amoskeag Manufacturing Company. Steam Fire Engines, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00299; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of The New England Litogrphic Company; Amoskeag Manufacturing Company. Steam Fire Engines from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00300; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00301; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
    - Refrigerators, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00302; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Refrigerators from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Refrigerators; J.R. Smith's Patent Furnace Grate Bar, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00303; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.
      Page image of Refrigerators; J.R. Smith's Patent Furnace Grate Bar from the 1870 Boston City Directory Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - A.N. Clark & Co., Leather Belting; Bruce & Chard, Organs; Simeon B. Smith, Civil Engineer & Contractor; J.R. Robinson, Steam Engineer, 1870; MS102.002.006.DO.00304; Sampson, Davenport, & Co.